<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.opalj.bdl.sdk"
      label="BDL SDK Feature "
      version="1.0.0.qualifier">

   <copyright>
      /* BSD 2-Clause License:
* Copyright (c) 2009 - 2015
* Software Technology Group
* Department of Computer Science
* Technische Universität Darmstadt
* All rights reserved.
*
* Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or
without
* modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions
are met:
*
*  - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
notice,
*    this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
*  - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above
copyright notice,
*    this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in
the documentation
*    and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
*
* THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS
&quot;AS IS&quot;
* AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED
TO, THE
* IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR
PURPOSE
* ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS
BE
* LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY,
OR
* CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT
OF
* SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS;
OR BUSINESS
* INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN
* CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
OTHERWISE)
* ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE
* POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
*/

Author: Thorsten Jacobi
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      /* BSD 2-Clause License:
 * Copyright (c) 2009 - 2015
 * Software Technology Group
 * Department of Computer Science
 * Technische Universität Darmstadt
 * All rights reserved.
 *
 * Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
 * modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are met:
 *
 *  - Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice,
 *    this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 *  - Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
 *    this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
 *    and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 *
 * THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot;
 * AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
 * IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
 * ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE COPYRIGHT OWNER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE
 * LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
 * CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF
 * SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS
 * INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN
 * CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE)
 * ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE
 * POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
 */
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Xtext" url="http://download.eclipse.org/modeling/tmf/xtext/updates/composite/releases/"/>
   </url>

   <requires>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.equinox.common" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.util"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.ecore"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.emf.common"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.xbase.lib"/>
      <import plugin="org.antlr.runtime"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.common.types"/>
      <import plugin="org.apache.log4j"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.editors" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui.ide" version="3.5.0" match="greaterOrEqual"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.ui.shared"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.builder"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.common.types.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.xtext.ui.codetemplates.ui"/>
      <import plugin="org.eclipse.compare"/>
   </requires>

   <plugin
         id="org.opalj.bdl"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="org.opalj.bdl.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
